(Leonard:)Sheldon, let's go!
To a hospital?!
Full of sick people?!
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't think so.
(Penny:)Okay, well, your friend and his
mother are there, we're going.
(Sheldon:)I can't.
(Penny:)Oh, don't tell me you're
afraid of germs.
(Sheldon:)Not all germs.
(Sheldon:)Just the ones that will kill me.
(Sheldon:)It's the same way I'm not
afraid of all steak knives--
(Sheldon:)just the ones that might be
plunged in my thorax.
(Leonard:)Fine, I'll tell Howard
you didn't come
(Leonard:)because you're more concerned
(Leonard:)about your own well-being
than his.
(Sheldon:)I would think
he would know that.
(Penny:)Okay, you know what?
You are unbelievable.
(Penny:)You buy all these
superhero T-shirts,
(Penny:)but when it's time for you
(Penny:)to step up
and do the right thing,
(Penny:)you just hide
in the laundry room.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll go.
(Sheldon:)Just for the record,
my Aunt Ruth died in a hospital.
(Sheldon:)She went in to
visit my Uncle Roger,
(Sheldon:)caught something and bit
the dust a week later.